无聊老生     诚意制作
根据源于人人影视同名作品调校修正 特别鸣谢
无聊老生制作  谢谢各位观赏
管制中心
Dispatch?
26号请讲
Go ahead, 26.
好的 请联系联邦航空局
Yeah, Contact the FAA.
告诉他们有个蠢货
Tell them some smart-ass is
在路上开喷气飞机 还不开灯
flying a jet plane around out here with no lights on.
收到
Roger that.
我听说你不打算去看比赛
Did I hear you ain't comin' to the game?
好像是说
Somethin' about "You don't
你不想为看一场橄榄球赛开五个小时的车
want to drive five hours to see a football game?"
我不喜欢凑热闹
Well, I'm not a big crowd guy.
而且必须有人留下来维持治安
Plus, someone has to stay behind, to keep the peace.
你要去划船吗
You going boating?
我是卧底
I'm undercover.
当然 雷 看上去真像那么回事
Sure, Ray. You blend right in.
星期天见
See you Sunday.
等等 你的车怎么办
Whoa, whoa, whoa. What about your car?
它停在消防区了
It's parked in a fire zone.
如果着火了
If there's a fire...
就帮我开走 但是记住 小心点开
go ahead and move it. But please, be careful with her.
白痴
Schmuck.
- 早上好 警长 - 早上好
- Morning, Sheriff. - Morning.
- 早上好 - 警长
- Morning. - Hey, Sheriff.
- 真是美好的一天  - 是啊
- What a beautiful day. - Yes, it sure is.
雷
Hey, Ray!
你穿便装我差点认不出你了
I almost didn't recognize you in plain clothes.
今天我休息 应该是个平静的周末
Well it's my day off. Should be a quiet weekend.
不要大煎蛋饼
No more of those big omelets, ok?
好的 但是你其实很喜欢吃
All right boss. But you know you like 'em.
是啊 但是
Oh, yeah, but ...
谢谢
Thanks.
- 这没关系 - 有关系
- It doesn't matter. - It does!
你好 伙计们
Howdy fellas.
你好 警长
Howdy Sheriff.
我猜外面的卡车应该是你们的
I'm guessing that's your rig out front.
你们今天运了什么
What are you guys hauling today?
- 汽车配件 - 没错
- Auto parts. - Yeah.
明天中午之前必须送到新奥尔良
Gotta hit New Orleans by noon tomorrow.
路途遥远
Oh, that's a long drive.
- 没错 - 是啊
- Sure is. - Yep.
买单 谢谢
Check please.
不用找了
Keep the change.
谢谢
Thanks!
我们得赶路了
We're 'bout to hit the road.
路上小心
Well, drive safely.
当然
Sure will.
谢谢老板
Thank you, sir.
谢谢
Thank you, boys.
他们肯定不大会算账
Boy, you sure are bad for business.
你想吃点什么吗
Did you want somethin' to eat?
警长
Sheriff?
不用了 谢谢 克里斯蒂
No. No thanks, Christie.
我得走了
I'd better get going.
再见
Bye.
再见 雷
See ya' later, Ray.
再见
See you.
亚利桑那州立博览会
That's the Arizona State Fair,
在格兰大道和麦克德尔路
where Grand Avenue and W. McDowell Road...
它能在大象身上打个洞 伙计
That'll put another asshole in the elephant right there boys.
该我了 拜托
My turn, come on.
等等 小心后座力 你可是第一次
Wait! Now watch that kick. She don't know it's your first time.
快给我 站一边去
Just hand it over. Stand back.
好吧 好吧 来吧
All right, all right. Here we go.
搞什么鬼
What the Fuck?!
不 不 不
No, no, no.
No, no, no…
放松 放松
Easy! Easy!
我提醒过你了
Hey, I warned you.
让我看看 让我看看
Let me see. Let me see.
怎么了 怎么了
What? What?
该死的
Shit!
鼻子破了吗 是不是破了
Is it broken? Do you think that it's broken?
应该是
It should be.
- 破了吗 - 是的 是的
- Is it broke... - Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
该死 该死的
Oh, shit. Oh, shit. Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
我还以为他今天休息
I thought he wasn't working today.
怎么了 雷
What's up, Ray?
雷 你好 真高兴看见你
Hey, Ray. How you doin' man? Good to see you.
有没有人能告诉我 我的两个手下
Can someone tell me what two-thirds of my force is doing out here
为什么要对着一块牛肉开枪
firing rockets at a slab of beef?
下午好 雷
Afternoon, Ray.
你有枪支许可证吗
Do you have a permit for that monster?
有的 有的
Yeah, right here.
拿块毛巾给他
Why don't you get him a towel or something?
他把制服都弄脏了 还有你
He's messing up his uniform. And you,
把你帽子上的牛肉弄掉
Clean the chunk of beef off your hat.
有吗
I gotta' chunk of beef?
瞧瞧 真恶心 谢谢
Oh, look at that. That's nasty. Thank you.
给你
There you go.
丁肯枪支武器历史博物馆
The Dinkum Firearm and Historic Weapons Museum?
是的
That's right.
你在这儿弄了个博物馆
You got a museum here?
有税单可以证明
And the tax returns to prove it.
每月第二个星期四12点到3点开放
Open every second Thursday of the month,
欢迎阖家参观
noon 'til three bring the whole family.
不好意思
Sorry.
给你
There you go.
谢谢
Thank you.
雷 我很抱歉
Ray, I'm really sorry.
雷 我们只是想找点乐子
Ray? We were just havin' a little fun.
小镇上没什么事情做 无聊死了
Not much to do in town, it's pretty dead over there, and uh...
我们需要找点事做
you know, we needed somethin' to do.
- 是吗 - 没错
- Really? - Yeah.
- 我有事情给你们做 - 好
- Well, I've got something for you. - Okay.
有两个司机刚刚经过镇上
A couple of truckers stopped in town.
他们看见我很心虚
They weren't too happy to see me.
他们肯定有问题
There's something off about them.
去给我查查
Run those plates for me.
好的 警长
Mine, Sheriff.
有什么发现就告诉州警官
If you get a hit, pass it on to the troopers.
雷 你看起来很结实 你经常健身吗
Wow! You're lookin' jacked Ray. You been workin' out?
我警告过他有后座力的
I warned him about the recoil.
把那该死的玩意给我
Give me the damned thing.
让我也来一枪
Let me have a go.
在我改变主意给你开张传票之前
Before I change my mind, and write you a citation.
我们已经部署好了
We've secured the location.
好的 都准备好了吗
Okay, are well all ready?
- 游戏开始了 老大 - 太好了
- Game on, boss. - Love it.
老大
Yeah, boss?
那个农夫有点棘手
We've got some trouble with the farmer.
什么 你们还对付不了一个农夫吗
What? Can't handle one farmer?
我跟你说
Tell you what...
我们开始吧
Let's get started!
我来跟他谈
I'll talk to him.
和农夫打交道是我的强项
I'm great when it comes to farmers.
你好
Howdy. How's it goin'?
你最好告诉我
Things goin' a lot better if you
你在我的土地上干什么
tell me what the hell you doin' on my property.
我叫布雷利
My name is Burrel.
我在做一个商业广告
You see, I'm shooting a commercial,
我想你一定在电视上看到过
I'm sure you've seen one on TV...
而你的土地
and your property...
正好合适
would be just perfect...
从我的土地上滚出去
Get the hell off my property.
我的公司会付你一大笔钱
The company I'm workin' for, gonna' pay you a lot of money.
你不必
You don't have to do a damn...
没听到我说的话吗
Did you hear what I said? Huh?
你就不想听听
Don't you at least want to hear...
我开出的条件吗
what I have to offer?
不想 你想听听我的吗
No. Do you want to hear my offer?
你马上滚出去 否则我就打烂你的屁股
You clear out now, and I won't fill your ass full of buckshot.
老人家 你最好把枪放下
Old man, you better put that piece away,
小心打到你的脚
before you blow your toes off.
我只是想谈谈
We just talkin' here.
谈话结束了 快滚出去
Now we're finished talking. You get out the hell out of here!
好吧
Okay.
这是你的决定
That's your decision.
既然敬酒不吃
You don't want to take the silver?
那就吃罚酒吧
Better take the lead.
我想说的是
What I'm trying to say is...
把前男友关起来真让我丢脸
It's embarassing to have to lock up your ex-boyfriend.
那是谁的错
Who's fault is that?
偷东西的人 你
The person who stole. You.
我是说 我们分手是谁的错
I mean, who's fault is it we're exes?
我们没有讨论这个问题
We are not talking about that right now.
我们在讨论
Oh yes, we are.
我是说 我们确实在说其他的事情
I mean, we're talking about something else,
但其实我们在谈这件事
but we're really talking about that.
你有阿司匹林吗
Do you have an aspirin?
这又不是医务室
This isn't the nurses office.
- 你到底怎么了 - 老天
- I mean, what is wrong with you? - Oh my God.
你什么都有 你又聪明
You had everything. You were smart,
又受欢迎 还是个出色的运动员
you were popular, you were a great athlete.
要不是大学时被踢出田径队
I mean hell, you had a full ride through college.
你还有全额奖学金
Had you not gotten yourself kicked off the track team.
你真的要这样吗
You really want to do this?
我他妈在伊拉克和阿富汗为国效力
Ok, I serve my fuckin' country in Iraq and Afghanistan.
我们没有在说战争 好吗
No, we're not talking about the war, OK.
我们谈论的是
We're talking about your
你酒后危险驾驶
being locked up for being drunk and disorderly.
我们都不在一起了 你还在乎什么
What do you care if we're not together?
莎拉
Hey, Sarah.
- 怎么了 弗兰克 - 你好 老兄
- What's up, Frank? - What's up, buddy?
真尴尬
It was awkward.
你们又开始约会了吗
Hey, you two dating again?
- 也许 - 没有
- Maybe. - No.
你非要把他关在这儿吗
Do we really have to keep him locked up in here?
是的
Yes!
为什么
Why?
因为我的长官说
Because the boss say I gotta'
要把你关到这个周末
keep you locked up for the weekend. That's why.
能告诉我怎么查车牌号吗
Could you show me how to run these plates?
蠢货 给我
Idiot! Give me that.
- 我只给你示范一次 听到了吗 - 好的
- I'm just doing this once, okay? - Oh, I know.
注意看
Pay attention.
雷 该死
Hey, Ray. Damn.
卡车的车牌号查到了
The plates on that truck checked out.
内华达州的 车主叫布雷利・ 托马斯
Nevada registry, The driver is one Burrel Thomas.
没有不良记录
Clean record.
很好
Great.
- 做得好 - 谢谢
- Good work. - Thanks.
但是我想你大老远跑来
But I'm sure you didn't come
不只是为了告诉我这个吧
all the way over here to just tell me that.
我得去别的地方
I need to make a move.
去有任务的地方
Go some place where there's some action,
去我能有作为的地方
where I can make a difference.
就像你以前在洛杉矶缉毒组一样
Like when you worked Narcotics in LA,
我只是不明白
I just don't understand how
为什么你要放弃一切 来到这里
you ever gave it up to come to this place.
过去四天我做过最紧张的事情就是
The most exciting thing I've done in the past 4 days is...
从树上救下一只猫
rescue a cat out of a tree.
萨默顿有它的魅力之处
Sommerton has its charms.
也许吧
Maybe...
我从来没有离开过这里 我都要疯了
I've never been out of it, and I'm going stir crazy here.
你能帮我在洛杉矶找份工作吗
Do you think you could help me get a job in LA?
洛杉矶不是你想的那样
L.A. Is not all you think it is.
听着
Look...
我明白你的感受
I understand that you want to move on.
你还年轻 你想要冒险
You're young. You want to experience adventure.
我像你这么大的时候
When I was your age,
也是一心想去洛杉矶
all I wanted to do was move to Los Angeles.
想大展身手 但是现在
I wanted to be part of the action. But now...
回首往昔 我的想法就不一样了
thinking back, I feel differently.
但是如果你真的想 我一定会帮你
But if that's what you really want, of course I'll help you.
早上好
Morning.
感谢你们这么早接到命令马上就赶来
Thank you for coming on such short notice at such an early hour.
这是一次绝密行动
This is a top secret operation.
45秒后 我们将
In 45 seconds, we'll move a prisoner
押送一个犯人去联邦死囚牢房
to Federal Death Row.
犯人名叫加布里埃尔・科特斯
That prisoner is Gabriel Cortez.
科特斯是自帕布罗・埃斯科瓦尔以后
Cortez is the most vicious cartel boss
最凶残的毒枭
since Pablo Escobar.
我们必须确保他不再重见天日
Let's make sure this guy never sees the light of day again.
所以要低调行事
We will travel underneath the radar.
开始行动
Let's do this.
护送车队在通道位置
Convoy is holding at position Alpha.
等待命令
Awaiting clearance to proceed.
提高警惕
Be advised.
该死 那是什么
Fuck! What the hell?
老天
Jesus!
- 全体下车 - 掩护我
- Spread out! - Cover me!
不要开火
Hold your fire!
开火
Fire!
停火 停火
Cease fire! Cease fire!
在屋顶 在屋顶 快 快
On the roof! On the roof! Move! Move, move, move!
- 约翰 我去守住小巷  - 好 你跟她去
- John, I'll cover the alley. - Good. Ok, you go with her.
飞虎队走楼梯 你们两个跟我来
HRT, you take the stairwells. You two guys are comin' with me.
你们去把电梯关了 剩下的人守住这个地方
You shut down elevators. The rest of you secure this place.
不让任何人进出
Nobody gets in or out.
- 好了 - 行动
- Ready. - Let's do it.
全面封锁 快点
Cover all flanks. Move, move, move!
跟上 伙计们
Pick it up, gentelman! Pick it up!
这边
Here.
1167 怎么了 我需要火力和空中支援
1167, What happened? I need back-up and air support.
医疗队
Medic!
我们走
Let's go!
飞虎队请回答
HRT report.
有两个人受伤 科特斯跑了
We've got two agents down. Cortez is gone.
停下 FBI
Stop! FBI!
拦住他  快拦住他
Cut him off! Cut him off!
站住
Stop!
把手举起来 不许动
Show me your hands! Don't fuckin' move!
不是他 不是他
It's not him. It's not him.
站住 FBI
Stop! FBI!
狗娘养的
Son of a bitch!
麦凯
McKay!
理查兹 你那边什么情况 告诉我
Richards, what do you see, tell me.
后门口没有发现异常
All quiet in the rear entrance.
我们现在检查巷子
We're checking the alley now.
约翰
John...
理查兹 理查兹
Richards. Richards.
请回答 理查兹
You copy? Richards!
别动
Don't.
你是麦凯 是吧
It's McKay, isn't it?
快当爸爸了吧
Baby on the way, right?
把枪放下
Put the gun down.
理查兹 理查兹
Richards! Richards?
- 有人倒下了 - 我去看看
- Man down! Man down! - I got it.
该死
Shit.
- 还活着吗 - 死了
- Yeah? Yeah? - No.
关闭半径100英里内
I want you to shut down every private airfield
所有的私人机场和飞机跑道
and landing strip in a 100 mile radius,
不管多小都关闭
I don't care how small.
- 那需要点时间 - 那就快去做
- That's going to take some doing. - Then get doing.
再去检查下
You need to check every
所有可以拍到那条街的大楼的摄像头
building that has a camera facing the street,
看看能不能拍到疑犯的脸
I want you to check that and
或者是车牌号码
see if you can get an ID or a license plate.
他给你多少钱
How much did he pay you?
他问你拿了多少钱
He asked how much you were paid.
拿什么钱
For what?
他不明白你在说什么
He doesn't know what you're talking about.
你以为我是傻瓜吗 我看起像傻瓜吗
What, you think I'm an idiot? Do I look like an idiot to you?
你想要我问他吗
Do you want me me to ask him?
不用 你问他为什么要穿这个
No. I want you to ask him why he's wearing that.
为什么要穿成那样
Why is he dressed that way.
你为什么要穿这个
Why are you dressed like that?
他问你为什么要穿成这样
He's wondering why are you dressed like this.
这是荷兰队球衣的颜色 怎么了
I wear the colors of the Dutch National Team. Why?
他说他是荷兰队的粉丝
He says he supports the National Dutch football team.
- 他妈的什么意思 - 足球队
- What the fuck is that supposed to mean? - The soccer team.
他穿的球队衣服的颜色
He's wearing their team colors.
你是在耍我吧
You can't fuck with me, or what?
好吧 我陪你玩
All right. I'll play this game.
荷兰人来自哪个国家
What country do Dutch people come from?
他是个混蛋 他差点弄断我的手
He's an asshole, he almost broke my hand.
他说你抓他的时候弄伤了他的手
He says his arm hurts from where you grabbed him.
他要拿什么东西 我担心我的安全
He was reaching for something, I was worried for my life.
所以我打了你 我下手应该再重一点
So I tried to hit you. I should have hit you the fuck harder.
一派胡言
That's such bullshit!
你终于说英语了
Oh, so now you speak English?
如果你懂西班牙语
If you knew any Spanish,
我刚刚就不会说了
you'd know I was barely speaking it a minute ago.
好吧 机灵鬼
All right, smart-ass.
凌晨四点你在干什么
What were you doing out at 4am?
这里是拉斯维加斯 老兄
It's Vegas, man!
长官 麻烦你来一下
Sir, we have something.
我是欧文斯 找哪位
Owens here, what's up?
警长 我是克里斯蒂 我吵醒你了吗
Hi, sheriff. It's Christie. Did I wake you up?
没有 没有
No, no, no, no, no...
我已经起来了 怎么了
I was already busy. What can I do for you?
我正准备开门
Well, I just came in to open up
但是发现牛奶还没送来
the diner and the milk hasn't been delivered yet.
这也需要找警察吗
Is this really a police matter?
帕森斯先生一直都很准时的
Mr. Parsons always delivers fresh milk first thing.
他起得很早 你知道的
He's a very early riser, you know.
我不是担心牛奶
I don't even care about the milk,
这周镇上都没什么人 但是
nobody's even around this weekend, but...
我印象中他从来没有不送货的情况
that man hasn't missed a delivery ever since I can remember.
我有点担心
And I'm worried about him.
你有打过电话给他吗
Well, have you ever thought about calling him?
那个老顽固没有电话
Stubborn ole bastard doesn't have a phone out there.
对啊
Oh that's right.
我忘记了
I forgot.
我担心他会不会突发心脏病什么的
I'm just afraid he's got a heart attack or somethin'.
很抱歉吵醒你
Sorry to wake you.
只是没有其他人在
There's just nobody else around,
我也不知道该打给谁
and I didn't know who else to call.
你做得很对 克里斯蒂
No, you did the right thing, Christie.
我马上派个人
I'm going to send a deputy out
去他那儿看看怎么回事  好吗
there and I gonna have him check up on him, All right?
- 谢谢 警长 - 没事 再见
- Thanks, Sheriff. - All right. Bye, bye.
科特斯和他的同伙丢下白色轿车
Cortez and his crew, they dumped the white sedan
然后分别上了两辆车
and they got into two separate cars.
我们认为 科特斯应该是这辆车
And as of right now, we think, that Cortez is in this one.
暂停一下
Hold that right there.
那是什么车
What is that?
米切尔在哪儿 他对车很熟
Where's Mitchell? He knows cars.
米切尔 过来
Mitchell, come here.
- 什么事 长官 - 放大
- Yes, sir? - Blow that up.
亚伦 这是什么车
Aaron, Aaron. What kind of car is this?
我想应该是ZR1
I think it's a "ZR1".
- 什么ZR1 - 雪佛兰ZR1
- What the hell's a ZR1?  - The Corvette ZR1.
这是特别改装的展示车
This one is a specially modified show car.
是带轮子的野兽
It's a monster on wheels.
前两天新闻有报道过
It was all over the news, like two days ago.
它在洛杉矶车展上被偷了
It got stolen from the LA auto show.
一般的跑车能达到700马力
Normally something around 700 horsepower.
但这辆高达1000马力
But this upwards of 1,000.
一个神经病开着蝙蝠车
I got a psycopath in a Batmobile.
我怎么才能抓住他们
How am I suppose to stop them?
炸了它
Blow it up?
要是有人质怎么办
What if there's a hostage inside?
好吧
All right.
把照片传给所有人
Let's get this out to everybody in intel.
这就是我们要找的车
This is the car we're looking for right here.
我们要找的车
The car that you are looking
是一辆改装过的雪佛兰ZR1
for is a modified version of a Corvette ZR1.
我看见照片了
Yeah, I'm looking at a picture now.
我们一发现就会通知你
I'll let you know when he reaches our position.
长官
Officer.
- 驾驶证和行驶证 - 好的
- License and registration? - Yes, sir.
驾驶证
Here's my license.
行驶证
Registration.
所有单位注意
All units, call it in!
等一下 小子
Hey! Hey! Hold on, cowboy.
不能偷偷摸摸的
You don't sneak up on ole man Parsons.
你知道他什么性格
You know what he's like.
帕森斯先生
Hey, Mr. Parsons!
我是杰瑞・贝利 我们只是来看你有没有事
It's Jerry Bailey. We just cme by to check up on you.
所以别对我们开枪 好吗
So please don't take any shots at us, OK?
该死
Shit.
- 走吧 去后面看看 - 好的
- All right. Let's check around back. - Yeah.
大神偷 先试试从门进去怎么样
Hamburglar. Want to try the door first?
帕森斯先生
Mr. Parsons?
我看看楼上 你检查一楼
I check upstairs, you check the ground floor.
科特斯刚突破了他们的检查站
Cortez just blew through their checkpoint.
幸好所有机场都关闭了 他没法飞走
But all airfields are closed, so he won't be flying out.
给我在牛头城设置路障 要滴水不漏
I want a roadblock here. Bullhead City. Nothing gets through.
他到底想干什么
What the hell is he tryin' to do?
从95号公路往南开
Southbound on the 95.
他以为能逃去墨西哥 门都没有
He thinks he's getting to Mexico, but that's not gonna happen.
他为什么不乘直升机
Why doesn't he take a chopper?
ZR1比什么直升机都快
The ZR1 is faster than any chopper.
不仅如此
It's more than that.
科特斯是第三代毒枭
Cortez, he's third-generation cartel boss.
他自诩不可捉摸  做事就这风格
He thinks he's untouchable. That's how his mind works.
他习惯用双手来驾驭一切
He wants to be behind the wheel. Literally.
什么意思
What do you mean?
科特斯十来岁就开始飚车
Cortez has been racing cars since he was a teenager.
他爸在锡那罗亚给他造了私人赛道
His father build him his own track in Sinaloa.
他在南美洲
He's been racing on the pro circuit
用假名参加职业巡回赛
in South America under a pseudonym.
我见过他开车
I saw him drive.
开得很棒
He's good.
安静
Quite!
我是班尼斯特
Bannister.
今天过得挺不错吧
Are you having a nice day?
抓到你就更不错了
It's gonna be.
这事只有两种结局 你猜会怎么样
This can only end one of two ways. And you know what?
是哪种我根本无所谓
I'm fine with either one of them.
不管你的特工小妞的死活了吗
With your pretty little agent dead or alive?
我可以把她剁成100块 然后一块一块邮寄给你
I can cut her up in a 100 pieces, and mail them back to you one by one.
你意下如何
Is that what you want?
你已经杀害一名联邦特工了 加布里尔
You've already killed one federal agent, Gabriel.
你再多杀一个的话
You kill one another, and I guarentee you
我保证你在天涯海角都没有藏身之所
this world is not big enough for you to hide in.
那你准备怎么向她父母解释
How are you going to explain to her parents
女儿被装在塑料袋里送回家的事情呢
why their daughter is returning home in plastic bags.
我告诉你怎么办吧 约翰
Here's how it's gonna go, John.
撤走你的人 给我让开路
Pull your men back and stay the fuck out of my way
不然你的特工死定了
or your agent is road kill.
我是无所谓的
I'm good either way.
让我和她说句话
So let me talk to her.
对不起 约翰
I'm sorry, John.
我搞砸了 对不起
I really screwed this up, I'm so sorry.
我会救你出来的
I'm gonna get you out of this.
好吗 别担心
All right? Don't worry.
我一定救你出来
I'm gonna get you out of this.
如果你敢挡我路
If you try to stop me,
会死很多无辜的人
a lot of people that don't have to are going to die.
你自己看着办吧
It's your choice how to play this.
我现在只想好好开车兜个风
Right now I'm just a guy out for a nice drive.
看来没法把他轰上天了
So much for blowing him up.
你他妈闭嘴
Shut the fuck up!
请讲
Yeah?
雷 我们在帕森斯家
Ray, we're here at Parsons.
我们找到了尸体 他被谋杀了
We found his body. He's been murdered.
我们已找到嫌犯车辆
We got a positive ID.
是一辆在95号公路往南开的银灰金属色ZR1
A silver-grey metallic ZR1 headed southbound on US 95.
确认人质在车内
Hostage is visible inside the vehicle.
- 他接近你了 警长  - 收到
- He's almost on you, chief. - Copy that.
别担心 我们准备好了
Don't worry. We're ready for this guy.
很多人都掉以轻心
A lot of people have said that.
科特斯总有法子击败他们
Cortez has a way of proving them wrong.
我要求你提高警惕
I need you to be alert.
你还得提醒你的人
And you need to remind your
车内有一名人质
men that there's a hostage in that vehicle.
接近亚利桑那州边界了
Coming up on the Arizona border.
- 他就快到你们那儿了  - 收到
- He'll be on top of you soon. - Copy that.
一切准备就绪
Everything's in place.
倒数五分钟 行动
Five minutes. Move.
坐好了 有场好戏给你看
Get comfy. I want you to have a good view of the show.
什么
What?
撤退
Fall back!
老天爷啊
Good God.
路障已被完全摧毁
The barricades been completely destroyed.
看起来这里像战场一样
It looks like a war zone down there.
多名警员伤亡
We've got several officers down.
我正在赶来
I'm on my way.
记住 不要碰犯罪现场的任何东西
Now remember, this is a crime scene. Don't touch anything.
明白
10-4 on that.
从破了的窗户来看
Ok, so the way I see it, we got a busted window.
这是场入室行窃被发现后的凶杀
All right, it looks like a burglary gone bad to me.
我觉得帕森斯走进屋子
I think what Parsons did,
也许是惊动了窃贼
he came in, and he surprized them maybe.
很可能是那样
It coulda been that.
你们检查轮胎印了吗
Did anyone check for tire tracks yet?
是他们先来的
They were here first.
我去查查
I'll go check.
- 别分散行动  - 遵命
- Stay together. - Yes, sir.
让我看看尸体
Show me the body.
就在那里
Right over here.
老天
Oh, Jesus.
入射点没有灼痕
No burn mark on the entry wound.
子弹洞穿头部
The bullet passed clean through.
一发手枪子弹弄不出这样的伤口
A pistol round didn't do this.
他们往哪条路去了
Can you tell which way they went?
往峡谷方向
Towards the canyon.
我们走
Let's go.
瑞士银行户头的三百万美金 我们说好的
Three million dollars in Swiss accounts per our agreement.
要知道 在我的国家
You know, in my country,
警察被收买以后都会说句 谢谢
the police say "Gracias" after being paid off.
你如果要继续像疯子一样开车
If you're going to continue driving like a maniac,
我能不演人质了吗
Can I stop playing hostage now?
不好意思
Sorry.
你要干什么
What is that?
找点刺激
Excitement.
什么
What?
该死 失去目标 我们失去了目标
Shit. Just lost visual. We just lost visual.
怎么会 找到它
How? How? Get it back.
我们四处找找
We're goin' around.
他跑了
He's gone.
什么叫跑了 给我接着找
What do you mean he's gone? Just keep looking.
你给我接着找 给我找到他
You gotta keep looking. Keep looking! Find him!
目标消失 我们会继续找
We lost him. We'll stay on it.
我靠
Fuck!
他在屋外被杀 事后尸体被搬进去
He was killed outside. His body was moved inside after the fact.
科特斯多久能到边境
How quickly can Cortez make the border?
照他现在的速度 65到75分钟
At the speed he's going, 65-75 minutes.
他正要去的那块边境
That little patch of border
肯定在峡谷深处
he's headed towards is mostly deep canyon.
能放大一点吗
Can you bring that up for me, please?
唯一的过境站在这里  阿尔戈多内斯
The only crossing point is here. Los Algodones.
我认识那的边防局长官
I know the CBP agent in charge down there.
他是个狠角色
He's a hard ass.
边境通道去年才重修过
And the border crossing was just rebuilt last year.
混凝土防爆墙加掩埋式伸缩型钢护栏
Concrete blast walls, in-ground retractable steel barriers.
简直是个堡垒
It's a fortress.
科特斯肯定不会毫无准备
Cortez isn't racing towards
就冲向目标
a target without a strategy to get through.
不管他有什么计划 我们都得做好应对
So whatever he's planning, we've got to be ready for.
向阿尔戈多内斯运输资源
Start moving assets to Algodones.
加强那个边境站的防守 没问题吧
Reinforce that crossing, all right?
这个小镇呢 萨默顿
What about this town? Sommerton Junction.
那里没有官方的边境站
There's no official crossing,
但那是离科特斯线路最近的地点
but it's the closest point in his path.
等一下
Hang on.
那里的峡谷太深了 不可能穿过去
The ravine is too deep to cross. It's a long shot.
但也别排除那个可能
Let's not ignore it though.
我给那里的警长打电话 告诉他躲远点
I'll give the Sheriff a call. Tell him to keep out of the way.
- 请讲  - 欧文斯警长吗
- Yep? - Sheriff Owens?
我是 你是哪位
That's me. Who am I talking to?
联邦调查局的约翰・班尼斯特  我们出了点状况
John Bannister with the FBI. We have a situation.
请讲
Well talk to me.
有个暴力逃犯正往墨西哥边境逃亡
I have a violent fugitive making a run for the Mexican border.
有很小的可能性
Now there's a small chance
他会试着穿过萨默顿
that he might try to cross at Sommerton.
虽然他不太可能去你那里
It's unlikely that he may be comin' your way,
但为了以防万一
but I'm going to send
我会从埃尔森特罗调一队特警过去
over a SWAT team from El Centro just in case.
无意冒犯 但我想让他们处理
No offense, but I want them handling this.
听着 我没空了 得挂了
Listen, I can't talk right now. I've got to go.
怎么了
What's up?
我不知道
I don't know.
联邦调查局的家伙说
The FBI says there's an
有个逃犯可能正往我们这里来
escaped fugitive that might be heading our way.
真该死  屋漏偏逢连夜雨
Shit, when it rains, it pours.
这不是巧合
This is no coincidence.
先是饭馆里那些家伙 现在又是这事
First the guys at the diner, now this.
这一切都有联系
It's all connected.
我得联系下贝利和托伦斯
I've got to reach Bailey and Torrance.
靠
Shit.
那边的灯是干什么的
What's that light over there?
你觉得那些是凶手吗
Do you think it's them?
你以为杀人犯傻到杀了人还在这附近逛吗
Do you think the killer's stupid enough to hang around here?
该死 给我手枪
Damn. Give me the Glock.
停车 停车
Stop the car. Stop the car.
那是什么玩意
What the hell is that?
贝利 托伦斯 你们在哪儿
Bailey, Torrance, where are you?
我们跟着轮胎印
We followed some tired tracks
到了镇子南边的峡谷边缘
to the canyon edge at the south side of town.
这里有些可疑人物
There's someone out here.
我们正要上前检查
We're checking it out on foot.
否决 你们必须马上撤回来
Negative. You need to fall back immediately.
你明白了吗
Do you copy?
给我对讲机
Give me this.
雷 这里有工地大灯 有个大工程在进行
Ray, we got work lights. Something big is going on here.
雷 听到了吗
Ray, do you copy?
站住
Stop!
杰瑞 快跑
Jerry, Run!
- 掩护我  - 快去
- Cover! - Go!
那边出了什么事
What the hell is goin' on out there?
我们正在交火 很多枪手
We're taking fire, multiple shooters.
我就快到了
I'm almost there!
戴上夜视镜
NVGs on.
关灯 马上
Kill the lights, now!
什么
What?
你还好吧 杰瑞 能到我这里来吗
You OK, Jerry? Can you make it to me?
没问题
Yeah!
可以的
Yeah.
不
No
贝利在那边 他中弹了
Bailey's over there. He's been hit.
- 我掩护你  - 快走
- I'll cover you. - Go!
给我拿家伙来
Bring me the gun!
贝利 我们走
Bailey, come on.
该死
Shit!
走 走 走 走 走
Go! Go, go, go, go, go!
有人跟踪我们吗
Is anyone following us?
没人跟踪 没发现有车头灯
That's a negative. I didn't see any headlights.
很好
Good.
你们还好吗
Are you both OK?
天啊 杰瑞 你还在流血
Oh my God, Jerry. You're still bleeding.
我没事 我没事
It's nothing. It's nothing.
- 雷 - 找到伤口 压住它
- Ray - Find the wound and apply pressure.
好的
Okay.
对不起 没事的 没事
I'm sorry. It's Ok, it's OK.
我听说制服上的血迹永远也洗不掉
I hear uniform blood stains take forever to get out.
我才不在乎呢
Yeah, well what do I care?
反正你得负责帮我洗干净
You're the one thats going to be cleaning it for me anyway.
你一包扎好就得洗
As soon as we get you patched up.
你觉得弗兰克看到我们这样
Do you think Frank would be
会不会羡慕嫉妒恨呢
jealous if he saw us the two of us like this?
当然 你告诉他
I know, you can just tell your
他只是浪费时间罢了 是吧
buddy that he's just wasting his time, you know.
我不和犯人约会的
I don't date prisoners.
是吗 他那么爱你
Yeah, he likes you too.
没错
Okay.
挺住 杰瑞
Hang on, Jerry.
杰瑞 挺住啊
Jerry, hang on, Jerry.
雷 开快点
Ray, hurry.
别睡着 杰瑞
Stay with me, Jerry.
你不会有事的
Everything will be fine.
杰瑞
Jerry
走吧
Come on.
雷
Ray
杰瑞
Jerry
莎拉
Sarah?
Sarah!
不敢相信他死了
I can't believe he's gone.
他死前还在和我说你的事
He's was talking about you, only minutes before he died.
他说了什么
What'd he say?
他让我对你温柔点
He told me to go easy on you.
还说你并不是无药可救
That you're not all that bad.
什么叫警察找你的麻烦
What do you mean cops gave you trouble?
- 什么样的麻烦  - 听着
- What kind of trouble? - Listen
你到底能不能准时搞定
Are you going to be ready on time?
当然
Yes,
准时搞定没问题
not gonna be a problem.
我希望你完成你的任务
I expect you to complete your mission.
我不想听到任何借口
I don't want to hear any excuses.
他妈的
Oh, shit!
- 我是班尼斯特  -  特警队还要多久到
- Bannister here. - How far is the SWAT team?
起码45分钟  怎么了
45 minutes or so. Why?
我需要你的帮助
Because I need your help.
你的逃犯正要从我镇上穿越国境
Your fugitive is trying to cross the border right around here.
你在胡说什么  萨默顿没有过境处
What are you talking about? There was no crossing at Sommerton.
他们会造一个
They're going to build one.
因为镇南边的峡谷非常狭窄
Because the ravine south of down here is very narrow.
这里有一大队人马
There's a whole team out here.
他们有军事经验和重型武器
Military background, heavy weapons.
他们正在峡谷间架设移动型突击桥
They're building a mobile assault bridge across that canyon.
- 是吗 你怎么知道的  - 我亲眼所见
- Oh really. You think so? - I know so, I've seen them.
我们和那些人交火了
We've been engaged in a fire-fight with those guys.
这个他妈的逃犯到底是谁
Now, who the hell is this fugitive anyway?
- 加布里埃尔・科特斯  - 你说什么
- Gabriel Cortez. - What?
你他妈的怎么不早点告诉我
Why the fuck didn't you tell me that earlier?
如果我早知道 我的手下也不会死
My deputy would still be alive if I would have known that!
我可没空跟你解释这些
You know what? I don't have time to explain every little detail to you.
你还是去门外巡逻一下就得了
Why don't you go out there and patrol, or something like that?
听着 我不认识你 我也不归你管
Look, I don't know you. And I don't answer to you.
这个混蛋
Son of a bitch.
再挂我电话试试
Hung up on me again.
你这个乡巴佬警长
Piss-ant country Sheriff.
菲尔 给我接特警队队长
Phil, give me the SWAT captain, all right.
好的
Got it.
再给我准备一份萨默顿的地图
And throw up a map of Sommerton up here for me.
我得好好查一查
I want to check something out.
- 长官  - 队长
- Sir? - Captain.
科特斯有可能会试着穿越萨默顿
There's a chance Cortez may actually try to cross in Sommerton.
你到以后 如果发现有桥 摧毁它
When you get there, if you find bridge, destroy it.
是 长官
Yes, sir.
移动型突击桥
Mobile assault bridge?
前面是特警队 你准备怎么办
That's SWAT up ahead. What are you gonna do?
死亡从不在你预期的时候到来
Death doesn't come when you expect it.
比如开赛车时
Driving a race car
或是在枪战中
or in a gunfight.
而当你晚上起来想喝杯牛奶的时候
Death is waiting in the kitchen
死亡竟会在厨房等着你
when you get up at night for a glass of milk.
我的侄女 我姐的大女儿 她是个好女孩
My niece, my sister's oldest, she was a good girl.
是我养大了她
I practically raised her.
那天晚上 她在厨房里用手枪指着我
Then one night, I find her pointing a Glock at me in the kitchen.
要不是她犹豫了一下
If she hadn't hesitated, it would have been
大理石地板上流淌的就不是她的脑浆 而是我的了
my brains splattered all over the marble floor, instead of hers.
妈的
Shit!
我操
别想预见死亡的降临
Don't try to see death coming.
因为你预见不到
You won't.
特警队来不了了
SWAT's not coming.
我们得靠自己了吗
So we're on our own?
好吧  那谁来阻止这个科特斯呢
Well then, who's gonna stop this guy Cortez?
这是联邦政府的事
This is on the feds.
他们押解的他 他们弄丢的他
He was in their custody. They lost him.
他永远都不该是我们的麻烦
He should never have been our problem.
或许是吧
Maybe not.
但如果他穿过我们的地盘 他就是我们的麻烦
But if he comes through our town, he will be our problem.
好吧
Okay, so
我们可以睁一只眼闭一只眼
we can turn our back for a half hour.
我们当然可以
We could do that.
如果你那么做 最好把你的警徽也扔到垃圾桶里
If you do that, might as well throw these in the trash.
雷 任它去吧
Ray, let it go.
我不能
I can't.
杰瑞因为那混蛋而殉职了
Jerry's dead because of that guy.
雷 你了解我 我不是个懦夫 听着
Ray, you know me. I'm not a coward. Look
为了杰瑞
I would more than happily
我很乐意和你一起将他们绳之以法
draw down on those guys with you, for Jerry.
但是科特斯 他太狠了 他有一支军队
But Cortez, he's out of our league. He's got an army.
听着 如果你们想袖手旁观 我无所谓
Look. If you guys want to just step aside, that's fine with me.
我不会因此而责怪你们
I'm not going to fault you for doing so.
但我不会让那家伙轻而易举通过我们的小镇
But I'm not gonna let that guy come through our town without a fight.
我就职时也宣过誓 雷
I took the same oath as you, Ray.
雷
Ray!
看起来你缺几个人手
Looks like you're a little short handed.
你会需要我的
You need my help.
你的枪法还和以前一样准吗
Are you still as good a shot as you used to be?
肌肉的记忆能持续很久
Muscle memory lasts a long time.
弗兰克 你以前经常半途而废
Frank, I've seen you start a lot of things you didn't finish.
杰瑞是我的朋友
Jerry was my friend.
我帮朋友从不半途而废
I've never quit on my friends.
放他出来
Set him free.
你现在是副警长了
Consider yourself deputized.
我不会让你失望的
I won't let you down.
好吧 好吧
Ok, OK.
现在咱们有四个人了 满意了吗
That makes four of us. You happy?
菲尔
Phil.
我要你查查我们部门所有人的财务状况
I want you to pull financials on everybody in this division.
包括我 全部都查
Including me. No exceptions.
科特斯有内应
Cortez has somebody on the inside.
我想知道到底是谁
Somebody who tipped him off when
在我们行动前向他泄露了消息
we were about to move, and I want to know who it is.
没问题吧
All right?
雷 我
Ray, I
我得告诉你件事
I gotta tell you
当杰瑞和我在枪战时
When Jerry and I were being shot at
我吓得六神无主
I was scared shitless.
我的手控制不了地颤抖
I mean, I could barely keep my hands from shaking.
那很正常
That's quite normal.
所有人在枪战时都会害怕
I mean, everyone feels like that during a fire fight.
告诉你个秘密
I tell you a secret.
我现在可能比你还害怕
I'm probably more afraid than you are right now.
那怎么可能
How can that be?
因为我经历了太多鲜血与死亡
Because I've seen enough blood and death.
我知道将会发生什么
I know what's coming.
你帮我联系华盛顿方面
I want you to ask Washington
提供我们萨默顿周边的
to get us real time satellite
卫星实时图像
imagery of the area surrounding Sommerton.
如果那个警长是对的
You know if this sheriff is right,
那我们就有一百多个联邦探员
and we've got a hundred federal agents
挤在阿尔戈多内斯的边境站
standing around Los Algodones crossing
百无聊赖 无所事事
with their dicks in their hands for no reason.
到那里最快的途径是什么
What's the fastest way to get there?
我们可以在麦卡伦机场申请一架飞机
We can charter a jet out of McCarren.
去办吧
Do it.
准备好了吗
Ready?
就凭我们这堆破铜烂铁
Yeah but how are we going to go up against
能对付那帮武装到牙齿的家伙吗
all that firepower with a bunch of shotguns and knives?
我有个主意
I got an idea.
要我入伙 你必须答应我两个条件
I got two conditions that need to be met before we do anything.
说吧
Well, name it.
我也要像弗兰克一样戴警徽
I want to be deputized like Frank here...
这样 任何我造成的或遭受的损失
so any damage caused to or by me will be official business
都将由萨默顿警局买单
of the Sommerton Junctions Sheriff's office.
把手放上来
Put your hand on it.
我在此任命路易斯・丁肯
I do hereby instate one Lewis Dinkum
从今天开始担任警员
who'll serve as deputy from this day forward,
直到萨默顿的民众
or until his services are no longer required
不再需要他的服务为止
by the people of Sommerton Junction.
- 见证人 - 见证人在
- Witness? - Witness.
还有什么
What else?
第二个条件
Second condition.
我还是想用我的老乔琪塔
Oh, I want to hang on to ole Georgetta here.
看来只有我才能搞定她
Seeing as I'm the only one fit to handle her.
好 行动吧
Ok. Let's go.
我是说 你也能搞定她 雷
I mean, you can handle her too, Ray.
还有你 弗兰克 没准你也行
And you too, Frank. You might be able to handle her.
- 谢谢夸奖 路易斯 - 行了 干吧
- Well thanks, Lewis. - Ok, let's go.
瞧瞧
Voila!
天啊 路易斯
Jesus Christ, Lewis.
老天
Shit.
真给力
What a beauty.
- 你从哪里搞来的  - 薇姬
- Where the hell did you get this? - Vicky?
我的纳粹小杀手 1939年的维克斯机枪
She's my little Nazi killer. 1939 Vickers gun.
疯颠颠的小骚货
My little crazy bitch.
我没法在合法的前提下进行试验
Of course she can't really fire in the legal sense though.
但我已经尽可能修复了缺少的部件
But I did run down all the missing parts for her.
所以理论上可以正常使用
So she could function theoretically.
这事只能天知地知你知我知
Course that's between us and Jesus.
山姆大叔就没必要知道了
Uncle Sam don't need to know nothin' about that.
- 还有弹药吗  - 还有几链
- You have more ammo? - A few rounds.
有多少带多少
Well bring everything you got.
你以为我们是要去肉搏吗
What do you think, we are fighting in the crusade?
有备无患
You never know.
五分钟之后在主干道集合
We meet on main street in five.
我们需要大量车辆做路障
We need as many vehicles as possible, for the blockade.
老汉丽埃塔由我来开
I'll drive ole Henrietta here.
你给所有东西都取了这种蠢名字吗
You have stupid names for all your shit?
喜欢的才取名
Only the shit I love.
行动吧
Lets go.
到了之后我会向你通报
All right. I'll brief you when we touch down.
保持联系
Update me.
边防侦察队正在组织队伍
Border Patrol is putting a team together
但他们一小时之内到不了
but they won't be there for over an hour.
- 国民警卫队呢  - 更久
- National Guard? - Longer.
军方呢
What about the military?
需要总统的命令
It takes a presidential order.
45分钟之内拿不到
We're not going to get that in the next 45 minutes.
科特斯必须穿过主干道
Now Cortez has to come thorugh Main Street
才能到峡谷那边
in order to get to the canyon.
除非他绕道阿萨莫拉
The only other option is Asamora.
托伦斯 你带着弗兰克和路易斯去那边封锁
Torrance, you take Frank and Lewis and block that off.
阿费和我去通知居民
And Fig and I are going to warn the civilians.
明白
Got it.
- 雷  - 大伙听好了
- Hey, Ray. - Listen guys...
有个逃犯会途径本镇
There is an escaped fugitive coming through town.
你们待在这里很危险
It's too dangerous for you to stay here.
我希望大伙都回家
I want everyone to go home.
你们听到我的话了吗
Did you hear what I just said?
我们刚点了早餐
We just ordered breakfast.
为了你们的生命安全着想
It's for your own safety.
跟你说话的是个72岁的高胆固醇患者
You're talking to a 72 year old man with high cholesterol
刚点了培根芝士蛋饼 还要多加芝士
eating a bacon and cheddar omelet with extra cheddar.
我像是怕死的人吗
Do I look like I'm afraid of death?
别看我 我跟他点的东西一样
Don't look at me. I ordered the same thing.
我刚开始做饭
Well, I just started cooking.
- 克里斯蒂在哪儿  - 去买牛奶了
- Where's Christie? - Went to get milk.
务必远离窗口  好吗
Just stay away from the windows, ok?
远离窗口
Stay away from the windows.
- 好的  - 这没问题
- Okay. - We can do that.
好吧  你想怎么做
All right. How do you want to do this?
把车都停到那边去
All right, let's put your truck on the far side
然后再多找些车来
and then try to find some more cars to use.
我有个更好的主意
I've got a better idea.
- 我们需要几辆大家伙  - 对
- We might need somthin' bigger. - Yeah.
这边要三辆 一定要堵死
Maybe three on this side. Have to be enough to fill it in.
你打算干什么
What are you planning to do?
- 退后  - 不行 丁肯 电线怎么办
- Just stay back. - No Dinkum, what about the lines?
只是电话线和电视电缆 供电网在那边
This is the phone and cable. Electricity's over there.
我不是这个意思 如果你切断电话线...
No, that's not what I mean. If you cut the phone line...
快下来
Geronimo!
- 快下来  - 后退 后退
- Geronimo! - Get back. Get back!
干得漂亮
Fucking perfect.
我们去找车吧
Let's get some cars in place.
真该死
Well, shit!
天啊
Jesus.
约翰
John?
- 你最好来看一下  - 什么
- You'd better take a look at this. - What is it?
国土安全部的实时卫星信号
The Satellite feed from Homeland Security,
这是紧邻萨默顿
this is the live view of the canyon
南部峡谷的卫星即时画面
just south of Sommerton Junction.
看那里
Look at that.
- 有座桥  - 对
- That's a bridge? - Yeah.
难以置信
I don't believe it.
那个警长是对的 他什么来路
The Sheriff was right. Who is this guy?
1998年 欧文斯加入洛杉矶警局
In 1988, Owens joined the LAPD.
在精英战术部门接受培训
He trained under their Elite Tactical Division.
在缉毒组干了五年 然后离职了
Worked Narcotics for five years, then he quit.
为什么
Why?
他为了追踪半吨可卡因的下落而搞砸了一个派对
Well, he crashed a party on some bad guys movin' a half ton of coke.
他为此得到了英勇勋章
He took home the Medal of Valor.
代价是挨了五枪
Five bullet holes for his trouble.
欧文斯活下来了 另外七人没有
Owens lived, but seven other cops didn't.
这就是欧文斯的背景
So that was it for Owens.
他大概是看够了流血牺牲 就离开了
Guess he's seen enough bloodshed, so walked away.
去萨默顿当了小镇警长
He went to Sommerton to play Sheriff.
谢谢
Thanks.
我们还需要两辆
Yeah, we need two more.
老天 你在干嘛 丁肯
Oh my God! What are you doing Dinkum?
- 你疯了吗  蠢货  - 冷静点
- Have you lost your mind, you idiot! - Settle down.
就快搞定了
I almost got it.
-丁肯 - 别闹了
- Dinkum! - Don't do that!
丁肯 丁肯 你没事吧
Dinkum! Dinkum, are you okay?
我的老天 你没事吧
Oh my God, are you all right?
汉丽埃塔呢
Henrietta?
成功了
It worked!
干得好 副警长 干得好
Nice job, deputy. Nice job.
雷 我们需要比这个更大的家伙
Ray, we're gonna need something bigger than this.
我有个主意
I got an idea.
- 托伦斯  - 已封锁阿萨莫拉
- Torrance. - Asamora's blocked off.
很好 让丁肯和马汀兹到学校来找我
Good. Have Dinkum and Martinez meet me in the school yard.
我需要你去老旅馆楼顶
And I need you to be on top of the roof of the old hotel
帮我侦察
to be my spotter.
费济 你去南边
Figgy, you go to the Southside,
看看建筑物是否疏散完毕  好吗
and check if the buildings are cleared, okay?
- 我马上回来  - 我去了
- I'll be right back. - On my way.
来玩场射击游戏吧
Time for a turkey shoot.
该死
Oh, shit!
主干道上有人从南边过来
I got guys on Main Street approaching from the South.
不要开枪 等我们到了再说
Do not engage, wait for us to get there.
收到 雷
Copy that, Ray.
这他妈是什么玩意
What the hell is that?
这下好玩了
This is gonna be a lot of fun!
左边去两个
I'll need two guys on the left.
你们两个去右边
You two take the right.
看见会动的东西就打
Shoot anything that moves.
不会动的也照打不误
If it doesn't move, shoot it anyway.
等我们办完正事
Once our work is done here,
就把这地方夷为平地
we're gonna burn this place to the ground!
克里斯蒂
Christie!
- 天啊  费济  - 克里斯蒂  快离开这儿
- Jesus, Figgy? - Christie, you have to get out of here, now!
你搞什么鬼  这些车怎么停成这样
What the hell's goin' on? What are these cars parked for?
瞧这妞的屁股
Look at that ass.
克里斯蒂 快离开街道 小妞
Christie, you have to get off the street, baby.
你为什么藏在车后面
Why are you hiding behind a car?
为了这妞屁股杀人也值了
I could kill for that ass.
该死
Shit!
快跑 快跑
Come on! Come on!
走  走
Go! Go!
趴下 趴下
Get down! Get down!
来啊 来啊
Come on! Come on, come on!
进餐馆 快进餐馆
Get to the diner! Get to the diner!
你就这点能耐吗
Is that the best you got?
瞧那个武大郎 居然还戴顶大帽子
Look at that squirrel with that big mother-fucker hat.
还不够刺激  拿大家伙来
This is getting boring. Get the big gun!
妈的 妈的
Oh Shit. Shit.
给他长点见识
Yeah. Give him something to remember.
我操
Oh, shit!
干掉他
Take him out!
Get him!
费济
Figgy!
干掉了
All clear...
这他妈是怎么回事
What the fuck happened?!
- 托伦斯 你没事吧  - 我没事 雷
- Torrance, are you okay? - I'm Ok, Ray.
但费济受伤了
But Figgy's down.
妈的
Damn!
这玩的又是哪一出
Now, what the hell is that?
欢迎来到萨默顿
Welcome to Sommerton.
好枪法 警长
Nice shooting, Sheriff.
汽车准备就位
Get this bus into position.
- 快点 - 知道 我在尽力
- Vamonos! - I got it! I'm on it!
已就位
We're in place!
趴下
Get down!
托伦斯 火力源在哪儿
Torrance, where is the fire coming from?
你们后面 餐馆旁边的楼顶
Behind you. Roof next to the diner.
- 掩护我  - 遵命 长官
- Cover me guys! - Yes, Sir!
你怎么样  警长
How are you, Sheriff?
老了
Old.
你的人生还长着呢
Ah, you got a ways to go yet.
天啊 警长 你中弹了
Oh my God Sheriff, you've been shot.
- 快来帮帮他  - 看到了 等一下
- Somebody help him! - I see it. Hold on.
别担心 只是玻璃碴
Don't worry, it's just glass.
到楼顶的楼梯在哪儿
Where are the stairs to the roof?
那边
Over there.
他想绕到莎拉后面 我们得提醒她
He's goin' after Sarah. We have to warn her.
给我无线电
Give me the radio!
- 无线电  -我们没有他妈的无线电
- The radio! - We don't got no damn radio!
我们只有双截棍
We got nunchuks though!
- 掩护我  - 掩护你
- Just cover me! - Cover you?
搞什么鬼
What the hell?
莎拉
Sarah!
这代表你原谅我了吗
Does this mean I'm forgiven?
可能吧
Probably.
该死
Shit!
老天
Thorzetta!
该死的畜生
God damn cowbell!
我操
Fuck!
老天
Jesus.
混账东西
Motherfucker.
禁止擅闯
No trespassing!
闭嘴 老太婆
Quite Granny.
萨拉查夫人
Mrs. Salazar?
警长
Sheriff.
多亏你了
Obliged!
打他们个落花流水  雷
Put the hurt on em', Ray!
好的
Okay.
- 费济 - 路易斯 你在干什么
- Figgy? - Lewis, what are you doing?!
费济在这里
Figgy's over here...
我操
Fuck!
雷
Ray!
去救丁肯 我掩护你们
You get Dinkum. I'll cover you!
找到你了
I've got you.
快点
Come on.
天啊
Jesus.
你在这儿干什么
What are you doing out there?
我是副警长
I'm a deputy.
路易斯
Lewis.
我在这儿呢
Hey! Here I am!
混账东西
You little motherfucker!
来啊 打我啊
Come on! Shoot!
你他妈在哪儿呢
Where the fuck are you?
王八蛋 你想玩吗
Little rat. You wanna play?
我最爱玩了
I love to play.
好吗
Okay.
该死的
Oh shit!
放下武器
Drop the weapon.
你他妈是谁
Who the hell are you?
我是警长
I am the Sheriff.
我到了
I'm here.
听见了吗
Do you copy?
准备好了吗
Are you ready for me?
准备好了
We will be.
近距离交锋是你的强项 不是吗
You're very good in close quarters, aren't you?
你很漂亮 理查兹探员
You're very beautiful, Agent Richards.
最能令我兴奋的事情
And nothing would give me greater pleasure...
就是证明
than to demonstrate...
我到底有多优秀
How good I really am.
但考虑到你的形象
But since you're still going
应该是一名死里逃生的人质
to need to look the part of an escaped hostage.
这是给你的离别礼物
Consider this a goodbye gift.
什么意思
What do you mean?
搞什么鬼
What the fuck?!
该死
Shit!
你想跟我玩吗
So you want to play?
那就来玩
Let's play!
然后呢
Now what?
狗娘养的
Son of a bitch!
该死
Fuck!
我要杀了你
I'm gonna kill you!
该死
Shit!
你毁了我的车
You fucked up my car.
你毁了我的假期
You fucked up my day off.
知道吗 警长
You know what, Sheriff?
你只需要让我跨过这条边境线
All you have to do is let me walk across that border.
每天都有成千上万的墨西哥人穿过这里
Hell, twelve thousand Mexicans come across every day.
有一个回去也无伤大雅
You shouldn't mind if one goes back.
你觉得如何
What do you say?
你毁了我们移民的形象
You make us immigrants look bad.
那好吧
Well then,
我们来讨论一下驱逐我的条件
let's discuss my deportation, shall we?
卡洛斯 等一下
Carlos, uno momento.
我的私人财务顾问
This is my personal banker.
只需要告诉他你的银行账号
Simply tell him your account number.
你的就增加五百万美金的财富
You will be five million dollars richer.
我们好聚好散
We will part as friends.
一千万
Ten million.
戴上
Put those on.
不然我帮你戴
Or I will.
这故事太老套了
Maybe once upon a time.
你的时代结束了 老东西
Your time is over, abuelito.
我的时代才刚开始
My time is just starting.
游戏开始
Game on.
你应该一开始就拿钱 老头
You should have taken the money, old man!
好 好
Ok! Ok!
两千万
Twenty million.
睁只眼闭只眼 两千万就到手了
Twenty million dollars just to look the other way.
我的尊严不是用来卖的
My honor is not for sale.
去你妈的尊严
Fuck your honor!
你被捕了
You are under arrest.
骑兵队到了
Here comes the cavalry.
约翰・班尼斯特 联邦调查局
John Bannister, FBI.
很高兴你们能赶来
Glad you could make it.
情况如何 科特斯在哪儿
So what happened here? Where Cortez?
警长去追他了
The Sheriff went after him.
比起科特斯 我更想知道警长情况如何
I'm more concerned about him right now than I am about Cortez.
你们两个运气不错
Looks like you're both in luck.
瞧啊
Look at that.
太好了 他干得漂亮
Good thing. Good for him.
最后一次 只不过这次轮到你吃惊了
One last time. Only this time, the surprise is on you.
我们走
Let's go guys.
约翰
John!
理查兹
Richards!
你还好吗
Are you Ok?
我还好
Yeah, I'm Ok.
非常抱歉 约翰
I'm so sorry, John.
他要杀了我 见到你太好了
He was going to kill me. It's so good to see you.
幸好他没杀你 我很高兴他没杀你
Yeah, I'll glad he didn't. I'm really glad he didn't.
不然的话我就无法享受
Because that would have cost me the satisfaction
亲手逮捕你的满足感了
of being able to arrest you myself.
你们不是早就习惯共同驾驶吗
I know the two of you are used to being driving buddies.
再告诉你一件事 瑞士银行账户
And for your information, Swiss bank accounts
可不像原来那样机密了
are not as secret as they use to be.
我们走
Let's go.
妈的
Shit!
所以我才开了枪
That's why I shot him.
我能走路
I can walk!
一个人在战场上英勇负伤
Just because a man gets wounded in the line on duty
不代表他就不能走路了  不用你们扶
don't mean he can't walk. I don't want that.
做得好 雷 马汀兹 托伦斯
Way to go, Ray, Martinez, Torrance.
我能走路
I can walk.
如果克里斯蒂实在想扶我的话 也可以
Maybe if Christie wants to help me, she could.
谢谢 小姑娘
Thanks little one.
随时吩咐 路易斯
Anytime, Lewis.
费济
Figgy!
抱歉 抱歉
Sorry! Sorry!
让我看看 让我看看
Let me see, let me see.
- 是50毫米口径的子弹  - 痛到死的50毫米
- That's a .50 caliber. - That's a painful .50.
我看看
Look at that.
你怎么样
What about you?
我很好
I'm fine.
拜托 别闹了 这是气枪弹打的
Oh, please, come on. That's a BB gun.
我们完成报告后马上离开
Let's finish the report and get out of here.
好的
Good.
我低估你们了 警长
I'll say it. I completely underestimated you, Sheriff.
没事
It's Ok.
你是个了不起的执法者 从不轻易放弃
You're a hell of a lawman. And you don't give up too easy.
你说得对
You're right.
这是我的家园
This is my home.
了不起
Impressive.
警长
Sheriff.
留着吧
Keep it.
你应得的
You earned it.
- 谢谢 雷 - 这也是杰瑞所希望的
- Thanks, Ray. - Jerry would want you to have it.
谢谢
Thanks.
雷
Ray!
我的车他妈的是怎么回事
What in God's name happened to my car?
下次别再把车停在消防区了
Next time don't park it in the fire zone.
白痴
Schmuck.